Passione is an extensive mafia syndicate.
At the bottom of an intricate totem pole
are groups of six to ten members, like us.
Above us are the Kapos, like Polpo.
Each Cape oversees their
own territory of business,
and each team has its focus, be it
assassinations, drugs, or otherwise.
While I am part of the Family,
I don't involve myself with
other team members and Kapos.
At the head of the Family is the Boss.
He has a trusted right-hand man with whom
he maintains exclusive communication,
so we have no means of
acquiring info about him.
Italian mafiosi hate attracting attention,
as it puts a target on their backs.
Even capos will dress themselves
like ordinary citizens,
and some even operate
front businesses as well.
The boss is the most secretive of
all, and never reveals his identity.
Any investigative effort
is immediately uncovered.
I know many who've tried and failed.
So, Giorno, if we ever want
to find our man of mystery,
we have to get him to notice us.
We have to gain the trust
of someone close to him,
or we'll never be able
to overthrow the boss.
Our first job is to improve
our standing in the Family.
We'll earn the rank of Cape.
But you and I can't do it alone.
We need a team we can trust.
If we want to beat the
boss, this is the only way.
The news of Polpo's demise spread
among Passione's capos like wildfire.
The guys in intelligence say
that it might have been suicide.
Nah, the big guy would never.
Bastard was in a maximum security cell.
No one could get to him.
Think maybe he betrayed the boss?
You couldn't find a more
loyal Cape than him.
There's no freaking way he'd do that.
I know, but what I'm most worried
about is who's gonna replace him.
I heard through the grapevine
that the capos are Fairy di Dust.
Apparently, Papa committed suicide.
Hey, eyes on the road! I got it.
Zillard has actually offed himself?
I told you to watch the road!
No one knows why he did it.
Maybe he was just tired of being a slob,
or maybe life in lockup finally got to him.
Whatever the reason, now we
know he was a waste of hot gas.
Damn coward bit down on a pea shooter
and painted the walls with his brains.
You sure he killed himself?
Someone else could have did it, man.
Well, the autopsy guy
told me it was suicide.
Any expert worth a damn can tell the
difference between suicide and murder.
There's a light, dunce!
Hey, you know the rumors
about Popo's fortune, right?
Rumors?
I know more about astrophysics
than I do any damn rumor.
Before Papa got locked up,
he converted some of his cash into
a nice stash of rubies and gold.
At least that's how I
remember the rumor going.
It's a hidden treasure Drive.
He had so much to own not even the bank
or the Family could handle it all No
one had the balls to look for it while
the inflatable idiot that was still alive
But now he's taking his eternal dirt map.
So his treasure is up for grabs It's
free money really and the way I heard it.
He hit five billion lira
Are you shitting me?
If I picked up that kind of moolah, I'd go
abroad with a bitchin' babe on each arm.
Get real.
I'd rather work my way up in the Family.
Once I buy my way to Cape, I'll live
a life most people can only dream of.
But where the hell did he hide it?
Isn't there anyone who knows?
No, although a thought
occurred to me just now.
The guy couldn't crawl out of that
cell without a crew of helpers.
You think an oaf like that could hide
five billion and loot all by himself?
He had to have had some help.
Some kind of loyal confrant type.
And as we all know, true
confrants are few and far between.
Polpo liked Bucciarati, didn't he?
Bucciarati?
You mean a tapista from Napoli?
That's the one.
If he had anyone hide it, it'd be him.
And now that Polpo's dead, Bucciarati
has probably made his move.
Especially with five billion
lira there for the taking.
I'm sure even he has a greedy
streak when he's in the mood.
Uh-huh.
Hey! Sookero!
That bastard actually hopped
his happy ass out of the car.
Did he believe that crap?
But if you're gonna try and tell
Bucciarati, I'd be real careful.
Word is, he and his
cronies are stand-users.
Fugo, can we please be done?
It's friggin' beautiful out there.
One day away from the
books isn't gonna hurt.
And besides, I'm just not
into it today, you know?
Don't say that, Narancia.
You should be commended.
Trust me on this.
It's not easy to ask
for academic guidance,
especially when you barely
attended grade school.
And yet, you still learned
your multiplication tables.
You can do it.
Just remember what I taught you.
You've got this.
Now then, multiply the six by five.
Six times five.
Six times five...
Is it thirty? It is! Bravo!
I knew you could do it!
You're practically halfway to solving it!
I get it!
Six times five is thirty! Nice! Huh?
Hey, what the hell is this supposed to be?
What, that?
It's a strawberry.
I can see what kind of
cake it is, dumbass!
It's not like I'd confuse the damn
thing with a chocolate or cheesecake!
That's not the problem here!
There's four slices!
They might as well have told us to die!
Another freak out, Mista? Shut up!
It's bad luck to take one of the
four pieces, everybody knows that!
Making a selection from five is okay.
Choosing from three is also a safe move.
But picking anything from a group of
four practically invites disaster!
When I was just a kid, a
neighborhood cat had four kittens,
and one of my friends ended
up adopting one of them.
Well, much to his surprise,
that fickle beast scratched my
friend's eye clear out of the socket!
Of course, he then beat that
kitty until it was dead and gone.
That's some idiotic superstition.
Just think for a moment.
If you eat one slice at a time,
eventually someone will have to
choose one piece from the four.
Exactly!
This is when the restaurant staff should
take the hint and bring out three slices!
Service here sucks hot ass!
You're more than welcome not to eat it.
No way!
I demand to eat Tortali Froggerie!
I figured it out!
All done, Fugo, see?
You're finished already?
Let's have a look.
What's this?
Did I get it right?
Fancy little punk shit!
You think you can mess with me?
How many times do I have to
keep teaching you this lesson?
Uh-huh.
Now he's definitely gone off the deep end.
Hey, Abakyo, are you going to eat
the rest of that cake or what?
What'd you call me?
A dense kagakatsu, was it?
You know, talking down to
people isn't very nice.
I'll cut you.
I swear I'll slice you to
pieces for the whole...
Dodo bastardo!
Enough, you fools!
Get it together!
I could hear your bickering
from the front of the building.
You're bothering the other customers.
I've brought along the new
associate we talked about.
Pay attention.
Don't dishonor us.
I'm Giorno Giovanna.
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
Sorry about that, Fugo.
I'm sorry, too.
Will you forgive me? Of course.
And I promise to study harder if
you'll please keep teaching me.
Listen, everyone!
I went out of my way to bring him here!
Show him some respect!
Mr.
Boucherati!
What is it?
You have a phone call.
Right, thank you.
Now then, all of you properly
introduce yourselves.
Capt?
I'll be right back, Giorno.
You should get to know your fellow
team members while I'm gone.
Sure thing.
Giorno, am I right?
Don't just stand there, take a load off.
Let's have a drink and chat.
They're waiting for you.
Crazy.
Bucciarati here.
Understood.
Is something the matter? No.
Bucciarati.
Bucciarati!
Do you have a moment?
Oh.
Signora Menini. Hello.
What's on your mind?
If you have time, could
you lend me an ear?
And speaking outside would be best.
Yes, of course, ma 'am.
I hope you enjoy it.
How old are you?
Fifteen.
What? Really?
I got two whole years on you, buddy boy.
Thanks for the tea.
Is something wrong?
You've already expressed
your gratitude for the tea.
What's with the sudden hesitation?
I believe we're past the niceties.
It's time to drink up.
Is it not warm enough for you?
Maybe he's afraid to down it because
he doesn't want to be one of us.
Huh?
Now what's going on here?
Nothing. Everything's fine.
He went to the trouble of making
a special cup of tea for me.
That's nasty as hell!
What'd you do? Speak up!
Holy shit!
He guzzled down every ounce of it!
You're gonna be fun to have around!
Major props, bud!
There's no way you
drank that stuff, right?
Go ahead and tell us how you did it.
If you tell me, it'll
be our little secret.
Spill!
Can't recall.
But you all are keeping abilities
under wraps as well, aren't you?
So this stronzo's a stand user.
I transformed my left front
tooth into a jellyfish.
And since it's 98 % water, it was able
to absorb all the liquid in the cup.
Can you transport matter?
Open your mouth!
There has to be a hidden cavity!
I don't know what it is,
but there's something
about Jonah that gives
him the unique ability
to charm almost anyone.
You think before you act.
A smart habit.
Have you told Bucciarati?
Kind of.
We're not exactly a cohesive team yet.
But we have no choice.
We have to act.
There's no time for indecision.
Focus up!
We're heading out, so
be ready! Huh? Where to?
Just follow me. Come on!
Hey, Bucciarati! Good morning!
Have a great day, Signore!
Hey, Bucciarati!
Drop by my shop again sometime!
I'll have to take you up on that.
And the car?
It's handled.
Just as I suspected,
people really trust him.
Hey, you know there was
no way to avoid that!
Bucciarati, this is one of my
dearest friends in the world.
Her troubled son has recently started
beating her and she's quite distraught.
Aren't you?
I see.
Well, no wonder you're upset.
I'll make it clear he crossed the line.
What's your son's name?
Thank you so much.
Deep down, he's a good boy.
But those damn drugs, they've changed him.
Bucciarati, I've lived in this
neighborhood for the past 50 years.
In all that time, I've never
been filled with such worry.
What would make him do such a thing?
I don't think I've ever been this scared.
Please, you'll keep all of us
safe, won't you, Bucciarati?
Bucciarati, you're one of us, aren't you?
I need to hear you say the words.
Yes, you can rest easy.
I'm going to fix this.
So you meant we were going yachting?
That's awesome!
When did you get a hold of a yacht?
We're renting one.
We don't get to keep it?
Hey, Bucciarati, hmm?
Do me a favor and stay away
from yacht number four, okay?
We'll sink to our deaths. Relax.
The yacht looks like
it's in tip-top shape.
Shut up!
If you like it so much, you take it!
We'd like to rent a
yacht if you don't mind.
Prego, prego.
Choose whichever one
tickles your fancy the most.
Just not number four. I know.
All right, we'll take
the one on the far left.
Certainly, signore.
I'll fetch your keys.
I'm interested in renting
the crap for three days.
How much? What?
Oh, I could never take
money from you, Boucherati.
Use it as you see fit.
Crazy mille.
Hey, old guy!
Get over here and ring me up!
Ah, yeah, this is the life.
Yo, Narancia. Hey!
Huh?
What?
Oh, well, uh, I was gonna say, hey, I seem
to recall you buying a bunch of drinks.
What would you say to selling me one?
What?
It sounds great, but I know
you're never going to pay up.
What's the difference?
Just give me.
Come on, toss me a cold one.
Why do I bother?
You want a cola or a fizzy water? Cola.
No, a fizzy water.
I want to see all the little bubbles.
All yours. Thanks, man.
Here, hold this book for a second.
You know, you're the best. Crazy.
Huh? What the?
Why the hell did it just stop playing?
It doesn't make any sense!
I just bought this thing!
Son of a shitter!
That bastard sold me a dud!
That cheap geezer isn't
going to get away with this!
Hey!
I think we've had just about enough
of the surprises, Bucciarati.
Where are you having this boat take us?
We're far enough away that
it's safe to tell you.
Our destination is Capri.
What's waiting there?
I take it we're not going
for the amazing views. No.
So then what's the point of all this?
Just lay it on us.
This morning the Cape
Polpo killed himself.
What? No.
That's crazy.
You're shitting me.
Why would he?
The why is inconsequential.
Polpo was an influential
Cape who courted death daily.
Hold on.
Let's focus back on Capri.
How are the two connected?
Polpo was stashing away
a vast personal fortune.
A fortune worth...
Ten billion lira!
Ten billion?
I'm currently the only one
who knows the location,
as he ordered me to hide the treasure.
That lira belongs to us now!
With capital like that,
we'll claim the rank of Cape!
Hell yeah!
There's no question about it.
My prediction will come true.
He's destined to become a couple.
This is an opportunity born
of perseverance and hard work.
I wouldn't expect anything less.
Well, what do you know?
Things just got a lot more interesting.
Where is it?
Where'd you stash that kind of
treasure on Capri, Bucciarati?
I can't say just yet.
The Family has long spread rumors
about the cache's whereabouts.
Until we secure the goods,
we must remain on high alert.
Bucciarati!
Hey, something's not right.
Say something, Narancia!
Narancia!
Quit messing around!
Guys, you're gonna want to look at this.
Just one lone shoe. Hand it over!
None of this is making a lick of sense.
I don't get it.
Where the hell could he have gone?
None of you saw anything
it was quick but it
looks like Narancia was
pulled into this box.
The question is how he
went where no that's
totally impossible i mean
he couldn't have plopped
straight into the ocean
could he Naranja where
are you hey Naranja this
better not be a joke?
Just say something, dammit!
Narancia!
Answer us!
Mista?
What are you doing, Mista?
Where'd you go?
Not again.
Come on, Mista.
Don't tell me you're in on this, too.
Fugo?
Hey, Fugo! What?
Oh no.
Avakio, Giorno, I need the
two of you to stick together.
We're under attack!
I'm certain of it now.
A stowaway snuck aboard.
And they have a stand!
But why all of a sudden here? The money.
Yes.
Word must have gotten out that
I know where the treasure lies,
and now they're after it too.
Someone else from the Family.
And how long do you think
they've been stalking us?
Is it possible that
they were at the docks?
Seems likely.
They knew I'd never mistakenly reveal
the secret, so they got impatient.
Our pursuer will kill you all
and try to force me to confess.
We're sitting sardines waiting out
here, so they're taking their time.
So you think the others are goners?
I'm not saying that, but
ten billion's at stake.
They won't hesitate for a
second to kill one of their own.
Listen, the others are still alive.
They're still somewhere on this boat.
I'm not at all certain if they're
being held hostage or not,
but they're alive at least.
What makes you so sure?
You happen to have any proof?
I won't just take your word for it.
I used my stand to turn
Narancia's shoe into a fly,
and now that fly is trying
to return to its owner.
If Narancia had been killed, the fly
wouldn't be hovering and searching.
Can you locate him?
He's still alive, but
something isn't right.
It's not descending into
the lower cabin or locker.
For some reason,
it seems to be completely fixated with
searching for Narancia over there.
Just what the hell is this guy's power?
Stop talking and listen.
Narancia is somewhere over there by
the cabin entrance. I'm positive.
But for some reason, it can't pinpoint
his location, so it's disoriented.
We should consider Narancia's location
and the enemy's one and the same.
In other words, the enemy is hiding, yes.
But they're not simply in
the shadows of the hull.
Va Bone.
Unless we can decipher
the enemy's abilities,
a single misstep could
cost us our lives. Yeah.
They may be able to attack while in
hiding, but that's also a weakness.
We'll study their stand and
learn how to take them down.
The real battle begins now.
Abakio, our secret weapon
might be your stand.
Why's that?
Do you have the ability
to solve this mystery?
Maybe.
Habakio!
I hope for all our sakes, you're not letting
a hang-up get in the way of survival.
Is that what you think?
I'm not.
I value my safety far too much.
I can't reveal my stand to just anyone,
especially a complete stranger
who has zero loyalty to me.
Pucerati, I don't know why you're
placing so much trust in this new guy.
But as far as I'm concerned,
he is no associate of mine.
If we don't crack this mystery,
the enemy will kill us all!
And how do you know that?
All of that crap is just this
outsider kid's random guess.
It's his cowardice talking.
He hasn't seen anything. Habakio!
I bet that bastard is just
hiding out somewhere below deck.
I'll force them out here and
give him a helping of payback.
Unless you die first,
which will likely happen if we
rush in without - Cork it, Kill!
You're just a piece of shit.
Come what may, I refuse
to give up my dream.
What the hell does that mean?
Go on. Solve it, then.
Don't let me down. Jonah!
Have you lost your mind?
No! Giorno!
That's where the enemy's hiding!
Merda!
Giorno's in trouble!
Apacchio?
Giorno Giovanna, you're one foley idiota
to go to these lengths to prove yourself.
This kid's even crazier than I thought!
The marines don't do
you?